<NewDataSet>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13750</productid>
    <productname>Dun &amp; Bradstreet Infra Award to Kishanganga HEP </productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November 01, 2018: &lt;/strong&gt;HCC&amp;rsquo;s Kishanganga Hydro Power project has received the Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet Infra Award in the Power Category. The Award ceremony was held on October 31, 2018 at Hyatt Regency in Delhi, where Mr. Arackal Benny, Project Manager &amp;ndash; Kishanganga HEP, LT GEN Anil Malik (RETD) - Vice President and Sanjay Kumar Arora, Senior General Manager received the award on behalf of the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; edition of the publication was unveiled in this event - &amp;ldquo;India&amp;rsquo;s Leading Infrastructure Companies&amp;rdquo; and thought leaders from the infrastructure sector came together to speak on &amp;ldquo;NextGen Infra: Building India of Tomorrow&amp;rdquo;. Shri Amitabh Kant, Chief Executive Officer, NITI Ayog, Government of India, presided over the event and handed out the awards.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DSC_4031_20181127_114632.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-27T11:46:32.96+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-11-01T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-11-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13749</productid>
    <productname>Construction Times Award to Kishanganga HEP </productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 28, 2018: &lt;/strong&gt;HCC&amp;rsquo;s Kishanganga Hydro Power project has received the Construction Times Award in the Best Executed Hydro Power Project of the Year 2018. The Award Ceremony was held on October 27, 2018 at ITC Grand Central, Mumbai where Mr. S. D. Jeur, Sr. Vice President &amp;ndash; Hydro Capability Development, Mr. Sanjay Dave &amp;ndash; VP &amp;amp; Sector Head - Engineering Management (CEMG) and Mr. Anuran Ghatak &amp;ndash; Sr. General Manager, Equipment, received the award on behalf of the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Construction Times Award honours the best and is exclusively for outstanding contribution done by the Construction and Infrastructure sector. This year&amp;rsquo;s chief guest was Shri. Uddhav Thackeray, Hon&amp;rsquo;ble President of Shiv Sena and the guest of honour was Shri. Rahul Shewale, Hon&amp;rsquo;ble Member of Parliament.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DSC_8417_20181127_114603.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-27T11:46:03.273+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-28T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-11-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13748</productid>
    <productname>HCC-HDC JV wins Rs. 2,126 crore Mumbai Coastal Road contract</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 03, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;HCC in a joint venture with Hyundai Development Corporation (HDC), has been awarded a Rs. 2,126 crore contract by the Municipal Corporation of Greater Mumbai (MCGM), for design and construction of the Mumbai Coastal Road Project, Package II. HCC's share in the JV is 55% (Rs. 1,169 crore) and the project is to be completed in 4 years (48 months).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scope of work includes design and construction of road, bridges, interchanges including reclamation and associated works between Baroda Palace near Haji Ali and the Worli end of Bandra Worli Sea Link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MCGM has envisaged the Mumbai Coastal Road Project (MCRP) along the western seafront of the city to decongest existing roads. This ambitious project intends to connect the iconic Marine Drive in the south to Kandivili in the north. It comprises of tunnels, roads on reclaimed land, roads on stilts and bridges with interchanges planned at strategic locations for dispersal of traffic. MCRP would cut down travel time of commuters by as much as 60% and the dedicated bus rapid transit systems (BRTS) lanes would encourage public transport, leading to fuel savings. The section from Baroda Palace to the Worli end of the existing Bandra Worli Sea Link is one of the three packages of the first phase of the MCRP.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>IMG20181021WA0008_20181126_035920.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-26T15:59:20.297+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-03T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-11-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13747</productid>
    <productname>Record Concrete Pour at FRFCF</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 25, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC team engaged in the construction of Fast Reactor Fuel Cycle Facility (FRFCF) at Kalpakkam, in Tamil Nadu, achieved a significant milestone by successfully completing continuous concrete pour of a massive 8000 cum of temperature controlled concrete for construction of a raft. It took 130 hours of nonstop pouring of concrete, at placement temperature of 23&lt;sup&gt;0&lt;/sup&gt;C, across an area equivalent to a football field. This incredible feat was achieved 19 hours ahead of schedule and is by far the largest pour in the history of the Department of Atomic Energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high-performance concrete of N45 grade with 10% fly ash has been used for raft concreting. The sequential method of pouring was adopted with over 500 layers of concrete being poured to avoid cold joints. The team had planned for the concrete pouring rate of 53.4 cum/hr, but with meticulous planning and implementation, they achieved an average rate of 58 cum/hr of concrete with the highest pour of 102 cum/hr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting at 14:00 hrs on August 20, 2018, the project team worked in shifts for 5 days till 24:00 hrs on August 25, 2018. The pouring was done 23 m below the ground level under varied weather conditions and amidst heavy monsoon rains. About 95 workmen were deployed per shift to carry out this mammoth task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a continuous feed of 8000 cum of concrete, the team required around 16000 MT of aggregate, 2900 MT of cement, 750 MT of ice and 720 MT of fly ash. Due to limited storage space, managing these inventories was a massive challenge. Around 30% of the construction material was brought to the site after the concrete pouring began.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The storage capacity of the cement at the site was 1100 MT. Hence, while 950 MT cement was brought to the site, nearly 35 bulker trucks carrying 850 MT cement were kept on hold during the pouring process. To supply 750 MT of ice, 15 temporary ice containers were brought to the site having a total capacity of 310 MT, besides in built facility to store 160 MT ice and around 270 MT ice was produced from the ice plant during the pour. Similarly, around 400 MT of the fly ash was brought to the site during the pouring process. Additional equipment was kept on standby to mitigate breakdown. The entire supply chain management has been handled with meticulous planning and precise execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s Indira Gandhi Centre for Atomic Research (IGCAR) had awarded the contract for constructing the FRFCF in August, 2017. This is the fourth construction contract that IGCAR has awarded to HCC, while earlier contracts cover the administrative blocks, township and the metallic fuel plant. The company is also executing DAE contracts at an integrated nuclear recycle plant for the Bhabha Atomic Research Centre at Tarapur and two pressurised heavy water reactors under construction at Rawatbhata.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>ConcretePouratFRFCF_20181126_035720.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-26T15:57:20.083+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-08-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13746</productid>
    <productname>2 Million Safe Man Hours at DMRC CC66</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; tab-stops: center 2.85pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 11, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; DMRC CC-66 Project (Dwarka-Najafgarh Metro Corridor) has set a record of completing 2 million safe man hours during the period September 20, 2016 till February 28, 2018. This achievement was highly appreciated by DMRC and Mr Gabdu Ram Choudhary (Project Manager-NJF) presented a certificate of appreciation to Mr. Pawan Padiyar, project in-charge on October 11, 2018. This feat is especially notable considering the complex nature of work in highly congested areas with numerous utilities and existing old structures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; tab-stops: center 2.85pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;This is the third contract for underground metro being executed by HCC since October 2012 under the phase III of Delhi Metro, having already completed three contracts under phase I and phase II of the Delhi Metro. The scope of work for includes construction of 224 meter open ramp, 219 meter covered ramp including a launching shaft, tunnel by EPBM method for 665 meter length, cut &amp;amp; cover 198 meter and station box of 288 meter. The contract also includes construction of one of the biggest underground stations, namely Najafgarh, which is 288 meters long and 30 meters in width. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; tab-stops: center 2.85pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;The RCC works at Najafgarh station is complete and finishing works are in progress. Excavation, base slab, wall and roof slab construction works is complete for cut and cover section and covered ramp. The client has expressed satisfaction over the progress of the site and the project is likely to be commissioned by June 2019. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>PHOTO20181011133636_20181126_035322.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-26T15:53:22.713+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-11T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13745</productid>
    <productname>HSE Excellence Award</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif'; letter-spacing: -.1pt;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 05, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC Ltd has been awarded the &amp;lsquo;HSE Excellence Construction Sector of the Year&amp;rsquo; at the India HSE Summit &amp;amp; Awards 2018 organised by Synnex. The ceremony was held at Hotel Four Seasons, Mumbai, on October 05, 2018, where Mr. Avinash Harde, Vice President &amp;ndash; IMS, accepted the award on behalf of the company. This years initiative is to spread awareness regarding the importance of occupational safety and health for workplace ergonomics and employee health and efficiency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;The IMS team has played an extraordinary role in reducing the number of accidents from 103 in 2012-13 to 28 in 2017-18. The team implemented Proactive Safety Observation Program (PSOP) in 2013-14, which brought a fundamental change in the way safety has been observed at all project sites. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;The Hazard Identification, Risk Assessment and Control Procedure (HIRAC) procedure was revised and a new procedure of Zero Tolerance and Reward system, endorsed by our CMD, has played an instrumental role in reducing accidents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;Along with the earlier method and subsequent to the successful implementation of PSOP initiatives, the team found that the root cause of every accident was &amp;lsquo;Behavior&amp;rsquo;. A new initiative named Behavior Based Safety (BBS) was launched to put and end to the root cause of every accident. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif';"&gt;With these range and sequence of proactive safety programs, HCC could significantly reduce accidents successfully.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>HSEExcellenceAward_20181126_034833.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-11-26T15:48:33.817+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-05T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-11-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13733</productid>
    <productname>Trawler Wharf</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>TrawlerWharf1_20181031_031028.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:10:28.307+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-16T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13729</productid>
    <productname>Impounded Dock at Haldia Port</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>HaldiaDock1_20181031_030953.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:09:53.597+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-31T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13721</productid>
    <productname>Ennore Port: Rock Quarrying &amp; Breakwater</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>EnnoreBreakwater1_20181031_030905.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:09:06.02+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13710</productid>
    <productname>DGNP Dry Dock and Wharves</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>image001_20181031_030626.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:06:26.5+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-23T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13705</productid>
    <productname>Cochin Oil Tanker Terminal</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>CochinOilTankerTerminal4_20181031_030543.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:05:43.723+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13701</productid>
    <productname>Trombay Chimney Works</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>_TrombayChimneyWorks_20181031_030424.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:04:24.957+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-31T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13698</productid>
    <productname>Satpura Thermal Power Station</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>SatpuraThermalHouse1_20181031_030341.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:03:42.023+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-31T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13695</productid>
    <productname>Ramagundam Chimney</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>RamagundamChimney1_20181031_030244.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:02:44.367+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13691</productid>
    <productname>Brahmapuram Diesel Power Plant</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BrahmapuramDieselPowerPlant1_20181031_030212.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:02:12.427+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13688</productid>
    <productname>Muzaffarpur Thermal Power Plant</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MTPP1_20181031_030034.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T15:00:34.143+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-23T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13686</productid>
    <productname>Uran Gas</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>UranGas1_20181031_025923.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-31T14:59:23.617+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-23T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150218</indexid>
    <emailid>avinash.harde@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Avinash Jaigovind Harde</fullname>
    <coverphoto>14181.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>M</gender>
    <DOB>1960-08-03T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>14181.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13685</productid>
    <productname>Rework or rejection accounting, if done properly, will help in cost optimisation</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: &lt;/strong&gt;H.O.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Avinash Harde and Team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TITLE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Rework/Rejection Accounting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the initiative: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rework or rejection costs in the construction industry accounts to around 3% to 5% in an ideal scenario. Sometimes the industry average goes as high as 10% of the total project cost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In HCC, the rework/rejection cost accounted is less than 0.1%. Hence, there is a possibility of not every project site accounting this cost separately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of the initiative: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For any rework, small or big, a fresh rework order should be generated giving details of the direct material cost, direct workforce cost, equipment cost and inspection &amp;amp; delay cost. Even the indirect cost associated with such rework/rejection should be accounted and booked in SAP/ERP.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of the initiative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These measurements if done properly, some specific remedial actions could be initiated using six sigma methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This would help bringing down direct and indirect construction cost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential for replication at other sites &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicable to all sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>ReworkRejectionaccounting_20181030_052916.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-30T17:29:16.84+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>avinash.harde@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Suggestion</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150389</indexid>
    <emailid>pawan.padiyar@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Pawan Shreevallabh Padiyar</fullname>
    <coverphoto>10510.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>M</gender>
    <DOB>1983-02-10T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>10510.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13684</productid>
    <productname>Vermicomposting is a renewable and environmentally friendly resource </productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;DMRC C 66&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team: &amp;nbsp;Pawan Padiyar and Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TITLE:&amp;nbsp; Vermicomposting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the initiative:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vermicomposting is a method by which com&amp;not;post or mixed manure of organic origin is pre&amp;not;pared by the use of earthworms. It is a controlled degradation of the organic wastes for the consumption of earthworms, helps in the recycling of food wastes, reduces the waste bulk density and the final product may con&amp;not;tain hormone-like substance which acceler&amp;not;ates the plant growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of the initiative:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project sites faces the problem of Food waste and garden waste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vermicompost is a renewable and environmentally friendly resource and is a faster method for reducing organic waste than traditional composting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A totally natural product, vermicompost can help reduce the need to apply chemical fertilizers, which is a less sound practice from an ecological standpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Vermi Composting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost/hrmsadmin/images/IdeaCentral/Vermi Composting1.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost/hrmsadmin/images/IdeaCentral/Vermi Composting2.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of the Initiative:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vermicomposting can also help to reduce the amount of organic waste disposed off in landfills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recycles wastes, Low Cost implementation, Helps the environment, contains more nutrients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential for replication at other sites &amp;ndash; Applicable to all sites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>VermiComposting3_20181029_094721.png</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-29T09:47:21.81+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>pawan.padiyar@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-28T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2019-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Suggestion</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13682</productid>
    <productname>Kudankulam Nuclear Power Plant - Animation Film</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/videogallery/7_KKNPP Animation Film_final.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T14:50:45.08+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-10-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-27T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Video Gallery</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13681</productid>
    <productname>Bandra Worli Sea Link Animation Film</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/videogallery/8_BWSL Animation Film.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T14:45:54.843+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-10-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Video Gallery</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13671</productid>
    <productname>Mughal Road</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MughalRoad1_20181027_020745.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T14:07:46.033+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13637</productid>
    <productname>Kolkata Elevated Road Corridor</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>KECP1_20181027_015602.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T13:56:03.127+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150335</indexid>
    <emailid>rajesh.k@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Rajesh Kumar</fullname>
    <coverphoto>13588.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>M</gender>
    <DOB>1968-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>13588.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13630</productid>
    <productname>Construction of temporary access to reach the inlet portal site</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Sawalkote Access Tunnel Project&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team: &amp;nbsp;Rajesh Kumar and Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TITLE:&amp;nbsp; Construction of temporary access to reach the inlet portal site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the initiative:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The superstructure work of the access bridge to the project site awarded to another contractor never got completed as the case went in arbitration and HCC was forced to construct 2 km long temporary access road along the left and right bank of Mandiyal Nala to reach the inlet portal site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of the initiative:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construction this temporary access road was a major challenge due to very difficult terrain, limited access, steep gradient, adverse weather conditions and very loose rock strata in the area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We could constructed the road of around 1 km on right bank side after overcoming these obstacles but the construction of left bank side road was even more difficult due to presence of very loose soil strata.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So the road on left bank side was constructed with support of series of stone wire crates placed in 3-4 rows manually to sustain the loose strata.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due to heavy rainfall, landslides and adverse weather conditions the left bank road got washed up and had to be constructed again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite all the challenges after six months we finally completed this road and mobilized all our machinery to start the tunneling works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Left bank road of Mandiyal Nala&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost/hrmsadmin/images/IdeaCentral/Left bank road of Mandiyal Nala.png" alt="" width="629" height="354" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Right bank road of Mandiyal Nala&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost/hrmsadmin/images/IdeaCentral/Right bank road of Mandiyal Nala.png" alt="" width="629" height="354" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of the initiative:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This road proved to be the lifeline of project and it is still the only access to inlet portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential for replication at other sites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>RightbankroadofMandiyalNala_20181027_032131.png</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>P</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T12:18:16.957+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>rajesh.k@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-01T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-05T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Suggestion</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13563</productid>
    <productname>Kaliabhomaro Bridge</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Kolia_Bhomora_Bridge_20181027_094723.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T09:47:23.8+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13516</productid>
    <productname>Bhilai Steel Plant</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BHILLAI_PLANT1_20181027_091830.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T09:18:30.64+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Buildings &amp;  Industrial Plants</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13504</productid>
    <productname>Sone Barrage</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>SoneBarrage_20181027_085906.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-27T08:59:06.503+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-27T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13263</productid>
    <productname>Baharampore Farakka Raiganj Highway (NH34)</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>bfhl_june10_2016_20181026_052230.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-26T17:22:30.28+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13256</productid>
    <productname>Kashang Hydro Power Project</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Kashang1_20181026_045711.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-26T16:57:11.773+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Hydro Power </categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13239</productid>
    <productname>Dayanand Samuel on RAPP Dome Lifting</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/videogallery/Dayanand Samuel on RAPP Dome Lifting.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-26T16:22:38.467+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-10-01T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-02T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>People Speak</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13226</productid>
    <productname>Chamera Hydro Power Project, Stage I</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>ChameraStageI1_20181026_041855.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-26T16:18:55.39+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Hydro Power </categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13225</productid>
    <productname>National Safety Award to RAPP 7 &amp; 8</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;September 17, 2018:&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size: 9.5pt; font-family: 'Lato','sans-serif'; color: #626262;"&gt;Rajasthan Atomic Power Project (RAPP) 7 &amp;amp; 8, Rawatbhata has won the runner-up award for working 4.13 million man hours without a fatal / non-fatal accident / total permanent disability, during the performance year 2016. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 17.3pt 0cm 17.3pt 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9.5pt; font-family: 'Lato','sans-serif'; color: #626262;"&gt;Mr. Dayananda Samuel, Group Project Manager HCC Ltd. RAPP 7 &amp;amp; 8 received the award from the Honourable Minister of State for Labour &amp;amp; Employment, Shri. Santosh Gangawar at a grand ceremony held on Monday, September 17, 2018 at Dr. Ambedkar International Centre, Janpath, New Delhi, in the presence of representatives of the various industrial undertakings, invitees and senior Government officials. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 17.3pt 0cm 17.3pt 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9.5pt; font-family: 'Lato','sans-serif'; color: #626262;"&gt;National Safety Awards (NSA) was instituted by the Government of India in the year 1965, to provide recognition to good safety performance on the part of Industrial Establishments and to stimulate and maintain the interest of both - management and workers for accident prevention and safety promotion programmes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 17.3pt 0cm 17.3pt 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9.5pt; font-family: 'Lato','sans-serif'; color: #626262;"&gt;These award schemes are operated by Directorate General Factory Advice Service &amp;amp; Labour Institutes (DGFASLI), Mumbai &amp;ndash; an attached office of the Ministry of Labour &amp;amp; Employment, and given under twelve schemes, of which ten are meant for Factories / Construction Sites / Installations under Atomic Energy Regulatory Board (AERB) and two are for Ports. The establishments are classified in different schemes on the basis of working of highest man-hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>NationalSafetyAwardtoRAPP78_September172018_20181026_015505.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-26T13:55:05.97+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-09-07T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13218</productid>
    <productname>Santosh Seevollynarayanan on RCC Dam Construction</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/videogallery/Santosh Seevollynarayanan on RCC Dam Construction.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-10-17T11:58:50.433+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-10-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-10-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>People Speak</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>151967</indexid>
    <emailid>user.m1@hccindia.com</emailid>
    <fullname>User m1</fullname>
    <productid>13167</productid>
    <productname>The Rabbit and the Turtle</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://localhost/hrmsadmin/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/The Story Of Turtle And Rabbit.mp4?rel=0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>TheRabbitandtheTurtle_300x200_20180920_090315.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-19T18:50:44.98+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>user.m1@hccindia.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-09-01T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2020-09-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Time Out</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13107</productid>
    <productname>Rajasthan Atomic Power Project, Units 7&amp;8 </productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>RAPP1_20181026_055622.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-18T11:30:33.167+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-09-17T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-09-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Nuclear Power &amp; Special Projects</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13101</productid>
    <productname>Pare Hydro Power Project</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>1_20181026_054157.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-18T11:28:25.117+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-09-17T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-09-30T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Hydro Power </categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13079</productid>
    <productname>CNBC TV18 interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Annual Results May 2018)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;div id="MainContent_rptwall_updreview_2"&gt;
&lt;div class="commentsbyuser slideInLeft animated"&gt;
&lt;div id="MainContent_rptwall_Panel1_2"&gt;
&lt;div class="user-comment"&gt;May 04, 2018&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="MainContent_rptwall_updreview_3"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/HCC_CNBC TV18_May05_2018.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T10:33:55.673+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-05-04T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13078</productid>
    <productname>India Today interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Davos 2018)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;January 23, 2018&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/AJIT_GULABCHAND_INDIA_TODAY_230118_2105PM.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T10:31:09.307+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-23T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13077</productid>
    <productname>Rajasthan Atomic Power Project - Units 7&amp;8 Dome Erection</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/videogallery/2_RAPP 7&amp;8 Dome Erection.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T09:44:50.943+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-03-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2049-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Video Gallery</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13075</productid>
    <productname>Infosec Maestros Award - 2018</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 06, 2018:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;HCC has been awarded Infosec Maestros Award 2018 for the second consecutive year. The awards are organized by infosecuritylive.com to felicitate organizations that uses IT security technology in an innovative way. Mr. Prasad Damaraju &amp;ndash; Sr Manager, IT Security received the award on behalf of the company in a ceremony held at Hotel Ramada Powai, Mumbai on April 6, 2018. Envisaging the security threats, network-based exploits, malware, and other threats, there was a need to have a complete visibility over the applications &amp;amp; network to protect against attacks. HCC&amp;rsquo;s IT Team invested in technologies such as antivirus software, firewalls and other solutions to protect the information &amp;amp; assets. To avoid external threats from visitors and guest, the organization network was segregated. By doing this, the visitors accessing internet on organization network will not be able to gain access to the network used by employees. Visitors and guests can do self registration through captive portal and have limited access to internet as per company internet policy. In future, the IT team will conduct information security awareness programs to keep employees informed about their role in protecting organizations information from cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Apr6_InfosecMaestrosAward2018_20180911_090632.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T09:06:32.84+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-04-06T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13074</productid>
    <productname>RAPP project wins three safety awards</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 05, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC&amp;rsquo;s Rajasthan Atomic Power&amp;nbsp;Project Unit 7&amp;amp;8 has received three awards by Nuclear Power Corporation of India Ltd. during the 47th National Safety Day celebration on March 05, 2018 held at the project site. Mr. Vivek Jain, Project Director RAPP 7 &amp;amp; 8 presented the trophy and Certificate to Mr. Dayananda Samuel, Group Project Manager HCC and his team. HCC won the Runner-up trophy of Project Safety Award-&amp;nbsp;2017 in the group C category (Project value over Rs.500 cr). The assessment was based on safety efforts put in by the team and best accident-free&amp;nbsp;safety performance during the&amp;nbsp;year. HCC&amp;rsquo;s Batching Plant site at RAPP has been declared&amp;nbsp;the Winner and Concrete Testing Lab the runner-up in the Project Housekeeping Awards in Group B (Auxiliary Plant &amp;amp; Shop Floor). In the individual category, 11 HCC employees were awarded the Near Miss Accident Award&amp;nbsp;for timely reporting the near misses and taking corrective actions to prevent recurrence of a similar incident at the&amp;nbsp;site. Companies like L&amp;amp;T, Punj Lloyd, IOTL, Gammon, Godrej, BGR Systems also participated in the competition.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>RAPPWinsAwards_600x400_20181024_094138.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T09:05:43.84+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-03-05T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13072</productid>
    <productname>Charosa Winery Wins Three Awards</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 13, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; Charosa Winery has been bestowed with three prestigious awards at the 6&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Indian Wine Consumer&amp;rsquo;s Choice Awards 2018 held at the Jyran, Sofitel Hotel in Mumbai on January 13, 2018. Charosa Reserve Tempranillo 2015 won the Gold award while Charosa Pleasures Cabernet Shiraz NV and Charosa Pleasures Sauvignon Blanc won the Silver and Bronze award respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nikhil Agarwal, CEO, All Things Nice has conceptualized this annual accreditation, which helps consumers understand new vintages and wines launched in the market, besides getting an insight about the different wineries in the burgeoning Indian market. The process involves bringing together all domestically produced wines in the premium category and categorising into a systematic tasting session. The wines were judged and scored by a panel of consumers who were not provided with the brand names or prices thereby creating an independent list of India&amp;rsquo;s best wines chosen by consumers themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Ch1_20180911_090117.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T09:01:17.25+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-01-13T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13071</productid>
    <productname>Appreciation for Fatality free project</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 05, 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC&amp;rsquo;s DMRC CC 30 project has received the Zero Fatality contract award from the Delhi Metro Rail Corporation Limited&amp;nbsp;(DMRC). The certificate of&amp;nbsp;appreciation by the client was presented to the team in a safety meeting held&amp;nbsp;on January 05, 2018 at the DMRC headquarters, at Metro Bhavan in Delhi. Mr.Daljeet Singh, DMRC Director of Works handed over the certificate to Mr. Prasdip Kumar, Project Manager of HCC for DMRC CC 30 project. Speaking on the occasion&amp;nbsp;Mr. Singh acknowledged that DMRC CC 30 project is the HCC&amp;rsquo;s DMRC CC 30 project first metro project in India to has received the Zero Fatality be completed without any contract award from the Delhi fatality. He appreciated HCC&amp;rsquo;s Metro Rail Corporation Limited efforts in adhering to good safety practices during the&amp;nbsp;construction process. HCC has achieved 8.16 million safe man-hours in the project.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DMRCCC30FatalityFreeAward_600x400_20180911_085853.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T08:58:53.663+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-01-05T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13070</productid>
    <productname>HCC wins first International Nuclear Power contract in Bangladesh</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 06, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;HCC in joint venture with MAX Group,&amp;nbsp;a leading construction company in Bangladesh, has been awarded a US$ 110 million (Rs.737 crore) contract by Russia&amp;rsquo;s State Nuclear Company, JSC Atomstroyexport, to construct Turbine Island for Unit 1 of Rooppur Nuclear Power Plant. With this, HCC has become the first Indian company to participate in the international civil nuclear market. HCC's share in the JV is 40% (US$ 44 million / Rs.295 crore). The project is to be completed in 40 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Rooppur Nuclear Power Plant 190 km northwest of Dhaka will be built with Russian technology and is equipped with two VVER Reactors of 1200 MW each. These reactors are similar to the Kudankulam Nuclear Power Plant in Tamil Nadu.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>KKNPP_PTI_20180911_085345.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T08:53:45.273+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-06-06T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2021-10-06T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13069</productid>
    <productname>Pare HEP commences commercial operations</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 21, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The Pare Hydro Power Project has successfully achieved commercial operations of both the units in May 2018. The first unit has commenced its commercial operations on May 21, 2018, and subsequently, the 2nd unit achieved commercial operation on May 28, 2018. Though the project has commenced commercial operations, the official inauguration will be decided at a later date by NEEPCO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pare Hydro Power project is a run-of-the-river scheme on the river Dikrong, a tributary of the river Brahmaputra. The project has a capacity of&amp;nbsp;110 MW and it consists of two units of 55 MW and utilize tailrace discharge of the 405 MW Ranganadi Stage-I project. It is expected that it will generate 506.42 million units of power in a 90% dependable year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The geographical condition of the river makes it one of the most compact hydropower projects in India. The river is in a horseshoe shape from the dam to the powerhouse which makes the Headrace tunnel one of the shortest with the length of just 2.8 km. However, the discharge of the river is quite high to the extent of maximum flood levels of 5000 cumecs. Hence the HRT has a large diameter of 7.5 M to generate enough head for power generation. The entire project from the dam to the powerhouse has been set- up within a distance of 3 km. Compactness of&amp;nbsp;the size makes it one of the most economical projects in the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The remote location of the project, poor accessibility, and unpredictable hydrology posed numerous hurdles in the construction of the project. The lead time of the delivery of major materials like steel, cement to batching plant and site location was unpredictable due to landslides and poor road conditions resulting in vehicles halting at several locations before reaching the site. To adequately cover the risk of flooding, the original design of the cofferdam on the upstream side has been modified from rock-fill to concrete cofferdam and the height of the cofferdam has also been increased from 6.5 m to 12.51m. Despite this, it was overtopped six times in different seasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maintaining just-in-time inventory was a huge challenge as even for smaller items the nearest suppliers in Guwahati and Siliguri were around&amp;nbsp;340 km and 730 km away respectively. Few special materials had to be procured even from as far as Mumbai and Goa which required even longer lead time. Rigorous planning and advance material management systems along with round the clock supervision made it possible to keep the required inventories and work was never interrupted for want of material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Poor geology prompted to introduce additional feature of the cut-off wall was introduced. The bedrock condition of the dam foundation was very poor. Hence, additional reinforcement has been used to strengthen the foundation that could support the weight of the entire dam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than technical challenges, managing and maintaining relations with the populace of the project vicinity for uninterrupted working was a bigger task at Pare HEP. The project management successfully managed it with the support of the &amp;lsquo;Village Elders&amp;rsquo; and continuously&amp;nbsp;motivating the team to overcome such situations passionately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overcoming all these challenges, HCC has successfully completed the project in May 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>PareHEP_600x400_20180911_084832.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T08:48:32.57+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-05-21T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13068</productid>
    <productname>Prime Minister inaugurates Kishanganga HEP</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 19, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Prime Minister Narendra Modi inaugurated the strategically important Kishanganga Hydro Power project built by HCC on May 19, 2018. HCC has time and again taken up complex infrastructure projects and created benchmarks by contributing to India&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure journey. The Prime Minister terming the project as &amp;ldquo;an engineering marvel&amp;rdquo; stands testimony to this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the project, Mr. Arjun Dhawan, Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer said, &amp;ldquo;The timely completion of this strategically important hydro power project along the LoC speaks volumes about HCC&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and scale of operations. Our team has soldiered to commission this project in the face of stiff challenges countering logistical, geological and climatic hurdles besides the odd shelling from across the LoC. This being the first major EPC project of NHPC, HCC has been involved in the whole lifecycle of the project from design through construction and commissioning. Our nine decades of experience in developing crucial infrastructure in India have equipped us with the expertise to deliver this complex project, which we are proud to have inaugurated by our Prime Minister.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 330 MV Kishanganga Hydro Power project was the first mega hydro power project awarded on Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) basis to HCC by National Hydroelectric Power Corporation Ltd (NHPC). The project has achieved several firsts in the history of Indian infrastructure construction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The construction of the project began in January 2009 on three fronts &amp;ndash; Head Race Tunnel (HRT), Power House and Ventilation Tunnel. The Kishanganga project envisages diversion of water of the Kishanganga river to an underground power house through a 23 km HRT, located 1.5 Km deep into the mountain. The plant will generate 1,713 million units of power per annum. Apart from the many states which would be the project&amp;rsquo;s energy beneficiaries, 12 per cent power generated from the project shall be provided to the State of Jammu &amp;amp; Kashmir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HCC team created a world record of the first successful Tunnel Boring Machine (TBM) operation in the Himalayan region and accomplished a national record by achieving &amp;ldquo;highest tunnel progress in a month&amp;rdquo; of 816 m in November 2012. While doing so, the team has successfully overcome several geological and engineering challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was critical to complete the project at the earliest in view of the dispute raised by Pakistan in the year 2010 in the Hague&amp;rsquo;s Permanent Court of Arbitration (CoA), arguing that the Kishanganga Hydro Power Project violates the Indus River Treaty. On December 20, 2013, the International Court of Arbitration gave its final award which unequivocally allowed India to proceed with construction of the Kishanganga dam in the state of Jammu &amp;amp; Kashmir.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>May19_KishangangaAerialView1_20180911_084732.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T08:47:32.23+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-05-19T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13066</productid>
    <productname>Parwan Dam Project achieves its first milestone</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April&amp;nbsp;26, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC has achieved a major milestone at its Parwan Dam Project on April 26, 2018, as it commenced the concreting work of the dam&amp;nbsp;20 days ahead of schedule after getting all due clearances from concerned authorities like GSI and CWC. As per the original plan, the concreting was to start on May 16, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;The Parwan Dam is a multipurpose project in Rajasthan consisting of a concrete gravity dam of 396.2 m in length and an 8.0 m diameter irrigation tunnel of 8708 m in length on the right&amp;nbsp;side of the Dam. The project is being constructed on river Parwan, which will join two districts, Jhalawar on the left and Baran on the right side, and is intended to cater irrigation needs of 1.31&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the tunnel front, out of 8708 m total length of the main tunnel, 5300 m passes under reserve forest, for which there was a restriction in fixing its alignment. Here, one of the major challenge was the in-time acquisition of land for excavation of adit tunnel and dumping of muck both at&amp;nbsp;adit and exit locations. The acquisition of land for these purposes was within the scope of HCC. The high land cost in the area and limited availability also posed another challenge. But&amp;nbsp;after micro level investigations, and with the help of the client, the HCC team could acquire the Government land available in the nearby areas&amp;nbsp;for this purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The excavation of 221 m adit tunnel started on March 15, 2018, and was completed in just 71 days which again was a remarkable&amp;nbsp;achievement. After completing the adit tunnel, the main tunnel work has begun. Three numbers of Boomers, one each at entry, adit, and exit locations are working simultaneously. Approximately 290 m main tunnel has been excavated till date with daily progress of 13 m, which is also very significant.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>ParwanDamSIte_600x400_20180911_084021.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-09-11T08:40:21.747+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-04-26T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13058</productid>
    <productname>Vishnugad-Pipalkoti HEP achieved river diversion</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 04, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC has achieved a crucial milestone at the Vishnugad-Pipalkoti Hydro Power Project on April 04, 2018 by successfully rerouting Alaknanda River through the diversion tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diversion tunnel is an integral part of dam construction. It is necessary to guarantee that the river can bypass the dam site during the main dam structure construction. The primary function of the diversion tunnel is to protect and ensure the site safety during construction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a Concrete Gravity Dam, the diversion arrangements comprising the Coffer Dam and Diversion Tunnel (DT) are designed based on the higher of maximum non-monsoon flow observed at Dam site or 25 years return period non-monsoon flow. The study of water flow through the tunnel generally defines the tunnel geometry. The tunnel cross section assumes generally circular or horseshoe geometry. Thus, it is important to trace the backwater curves for diversion tunnel with the goal of establishing the various flow depths along the structure allowing the flow classification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The circular diversion tunnel at Vishnugad-Pipalkoti HEP is of 10.5 m diameter and 496 m in length. This tunnel has Rectangular Box structures of 52 m &amp;amp; 12 m at inlet and outlet ends to facilitate safe passage for vehicular movement for further construction of coffer dams and main dam. The box structures also provide a gentle hydraulic jump for the rushing water coming through diversion tunnel inlet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lining of diversion tunnel comprised of following stages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversion tunnel lining through the kerb, overt and invert (458 m)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bottom DSPT lining through the sacrificial liner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversion cum spill tunnel &amp;amp; diversion tunnel junction concreting by conventional shuttering (28 m)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inlet box structure concreting by staging &amp;amp; shuttering of raft, walls &amp;amp; top slab (52 m)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outlet box structure concreting by staging &amp;amp; shuttering of raft, walls &amp;amp; top slab (12 m)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outlet transition portion through special shuttering (10 m)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact grouting in diversion tunnel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consolidation grouting in diversion tunnel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major impediment faced by the engineers was the predominant and prolonged monsoon season which caused heavy waterlogging. The diversion tunnel being close to river water level was severely affected by seasonal rains which led to frequent flooding of the tunnel. A lot of time was lost in dewatering the tunnel area. Even the approach road to diversion tunnel outlet area was washed away along with the crate walls, bringing entire works in outlet region to a standstill until the road was repaired to resume works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another challenge was the constraint of a single access to resources (primarily equipment) through inlet end. Since the outlet end was blocked, excavation &amp;amp; mucking of inlet box structure by cut &amp;amp; cover method &amp;amp; gantry lining of diversion tunnel could not be done simultaneously. Overcoming all these challenges the team successfully completed the diversion tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Apr4_VishnugadRiverDiversion1_20180704_113615.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-07-04T11:36:15.883+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-04-04T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13057</productid>
    <productname>Construction Safety Professionals Meet</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 21, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Integrated Management System (IMS) department of HCC organised the first-of-its-kind Construction Safety Professional Meet, on March 21, 2018, with an aim to develop an integrated approach to reduce accidents in the construction industry. The event brought together 35 safety professionals and consultants representing 15 organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting was chaired by Mr. V B Sant, Director General - National Safety Council and Dr. Kaila, Director - Forum of Behavioural Safety, an expert advisory firm. The meet was a common platform for the organizations to share their safety initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addressing the gathering Mr. Sant said, &amp;ldquo;Being an unorganized sector, the construction industry in India faces severe safety challenges due to ever-changing work locations and work environment. The fatal injury rate for the construction industry is higher than the national average of all industries put together.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He assured that, in future, National Safety Council will closely work with the construction industry to strengthen the safety culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kaila shared the success stories in the manufacturing industry and elaborated on how Behaviour Based Safety programmes have helped the manufacturing industry to considerably reduce accidents. He opined that very few construction companies have implemented BBS programme and urged that more and more construction companies should adopt BBS programme. Other speakers included Mr. Satnam Singh from Crane Brainz who shared prevailing scenario of construction equipment, Mr. A K Kulkarni, a safety specialist who talked about role and responsibility of safety professionals, Lt. Cdr. Mahendra Kakade (retd) who shared innovative ways to achieve zero accident at projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Avinash Harde, Vice President, IMS, HCC, in his concluding remarks said, &amp;ldquo;Unlike manufacturing sector which has permanent workforce over a longer duration of time, the construction industry is saddled with the challenges of the migratory workforce that work for a shorter duration. Hence while tackling the issues of safety in construction the outdated manufacturing model won&amp;rsquo;t work. We need to innovate and try out newer ways to implement safety initiatives on a continuous and regular basis. Hence it is imperative that we meet on a regular basis to share newer ideas and initiatives.&amp;rdquo; All agreed to meet once in a quarter under the banner of Construction Safety Professional Meet.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Mar21_ConstructionSafetyProfessionalsMeet_20180704_113445.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-07-04T11:34:45.99+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-03-21T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13056</productid>
    <productname>DMRC CC 30 inaugurated</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 14, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; Delhi Metro&amp;rsquo;s Pink Corridor from the Majlis Park station to Durgabal Deshmukh South Campus station, which consists of CC 30 package built by HCC, has been formally inaugurated for passenger services on March 14, 2018 by Mr. Hardeep Singh Puri, the Union Minister of State (Independent Incharge) for Housing and Urban Affairs and Mr. Arvind Kejriwal, the Chief Minister of Delhi. During the inauguration, Dr. Harsh Vardhan, the Union Minister of Science and Technology, Earth Sciences, Environment, Forests and Climate Change, and other senior dignitaries were also present. The 21.56 km long corridor is the longest stretch opened as part of Delhi Metro&amp;rsquo;s Phase III so far.&amp;nbsp; It consists of 12 stations and will connect the Delhi University&amp;rsquo;s South Campus for the first time by Metro. Out of 12 stations, HCC has constructed two stations - Shalimar Bagh (underground) and Netaji Subhash Place (semi underground). The DMRC has praised HCC&amp;rsquo;s work through an appreciation letter for completing the critical works within a short period of time with great efficiency, safety, and quality. The dedication, professionalism of the team in undertaking the critical works as well as the determination of the project leadership were also appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Mar14_DMRCCC_30Inauguration_20180704_113036.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-07-04T11:30:36.38+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-03-14T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2018-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13055</productid>
    <productname>HCC erects first of its kind dome at RAPP Unit 7</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 25, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC has successfully completed a major milestone at the Rajasthan Atomic Power Project (RAPP) in Rawatbhata, Rajasthan on February 25, 2018, by lifting and erecting the massive dome of the reactor building of Unit 7 with a remarkable precision. HCC has undertaken the construction of Units 7 &amp;amp; 8 (2x700 MW) of the Pressurized Heavy Water Reactors for the main plant of the RAPP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than 250 officers of Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL), Rajasthan Atomic Power Station (RAPS) and HCC witnessed this achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The single piece torispherical dish-shaped dome weighs 346 metric tons. It is 49 m in diameter and about 8 meters tall at the center. The dome was assembled using 53 panels joined seamlessly by welding. The total length of the weld carried out in the fabrication and assembly of the dome was around 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire process took 11 months and was completed in three stages. First, panels were fabricated in the fabrication yard followed by the assembly of panels near the reactor building and finally welding them together to form the huge dome. The fabrication of panels was so precise that the assembling of panels didn&amp;rsquo;t require any force fitting. This was appreciated by the senior officials including designers of NPCIL and Atomic Energy Regulatory Board (AERB).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A special 1350 tons LIEBHERR LR 11350 Crawler Crane was used to erect the dome. A no-load mock-up of the crane was carried out in the initial stage to finalize the crane position considering the center of the dome at assembly and center of the reactor and to check the vertical clearance required for the erection of dome. On February 23, 2018, the dome was lifted twice and held in position for 30 minutes and 120 minutes separately to release the stress and checked for any distortion at predefined control points. In order to avoid any last minute trouble the sequence of lifting, marching and swinging were meticulously worked out well in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the two tower cranes were lowered to below ring beam level to ensure adequate clearance from the bottom of the dome as well as from the mast and boom of the crane during the swinging and lowering operation. The time of erection was decided after studying the hourly wind speed variations and data available from the Project Meteorological laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actual lifting was started at 7:46 am and the placing in position including arresting of support points, was completed by 11.10 am - in just three and half hours. After erecting, the critical controlling points of reactor alignment (CB/CR) and dome crown elevation were checked and found that same were matched precisely with +/- 2 mm accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kudos to the RAPP project team for completing the herculean task in the first attempt.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Feb25_RAPPDomeLifting_20180704_112857.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-07-04T11:28:57.793+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-02-25T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-07-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13054</productid>
    <productname>2nd TBM launched at Mumbai Metro</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 21, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; HCC successfully launched its second tunnel boring machine (TBM) at Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus (CSMT) site of Mumbai Metro Line 3 package UGC-2 project on February 21, 2018. Manufactured by Terratec, it is a single shield dual-mode hard rock TBM, equipped to operate in both, open or closed mode in the predominantly fresh and slightly to moderately weathered Basalt and Breccia as earlier anticipated in the Mumbai Metro project. Mumbai Metro Rail Corporation Ltd has named these TBMs as Vaitarna I and Vaitarna II. After arriving at Mumbai Port on December 30, 2017 from China, the Vaitarna II was shifted to the CSMT site on January 06, 2018. After assembling at the site, the initial drive for the Vaitarna II was completed on April 02, 2018 and the main drive was started from May 02, 2018. Terratec will provide support to the TBM team for 6 months or initial 150 m drilling. It is expected to achieve an average drilling rate of around 13 m per day over the course of its 3.827 km drive from Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus to Mumbai Central via the station boxes at Kalbadevi, Girgaon and Grant Road. Vaitarna I was launched in December 2017 and has already completed 333 m of the tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>Feb21_SecondTBMLaunchatCSMT_20180704_112626.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-07-04T11:26:27.353+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-02-21T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-07-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13001</productid>
    <productname>EPC World Award 2017</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December&amp;nbsp;20, 2017:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;HCC&amp;rsquo;s Sainj Hydro Power Project has been awarded the &amp;ldquo;Outstanding Contribution in Power Generation&amp;rdquo; at the 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;EPC World Award 2017 held on December 20, 2017, at Hotel &amp;ldquo;The Ashok, New Delhi. Mr. S. D Jeur, Sr. Vice President &amp;ndash; Hydro Capability Development received the award on behalf of the Company in the presence of eminent stalwarts of the Infrastructure &amp;amp; Construction industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the third award bestowed to the Sainj Hydro Power Project. Earlier in the year, the project had bagged two more industry awards including the Construction Times Award for the best executed project and Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet Infra Award for the best project in the power category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sainj Hydro Power project is a run-of-the-river development on Sainj river - a tributary of Beas river in Kullu district of Himachal Pradesh. HCC was responsible for planning, design &amp;amp; engineering, execution of civil &amp;amp; infrastructure works, as well as erection &amp;amp; commissioning of hydro-mechanical components.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DSC_0206_20180228_060036.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-02-28T18:00:36.943+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-20T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Achievements</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>13000</productid>
    <productname>Amit Uplenchwar appointed CEO of HCCs E&amp;C Business</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;HCC has appointed Mr. Amit Uplenchwar as the Chief Executive Officer of its Engineering &amp;amp; Construction (E&amp;amp;C) business effective January 31, 2018, pursuant to retirement of Mr. Arun Karambelkar from the Company on completion of his tenure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Uplenchwar is a highly acclaimed business leader with deep experience in the Infrastructure and Energy Sector, he has handled areas of operations, revenue, profitability &amp;amp; growth, business development and project management. Mr. Uplenchwar has joined HCC from Adani Ports &amp;amp; SEZ Group where, as a President, he was heading Business Development of all 10 Ports of Adani Group. Additionally, he was also responsible for Strategy and was part of the team deciding on investments in new businesses. He was also heading mergers and acquisitions for Adani Ports and SEZ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining Adani Group, Mr. Uplenchwar had been working as&amp;nbsp; Managing Director of the EPC division of Dodsal Engineering &amp;amp; Construction, Dubai, UAE. In his decade-long tenure with Dodsal, Mr. Uplenchwar held various other positions, including Deputy Managing Director &amp;ndash; Business Development, Executive Director &amp;ndash; Corporate etc. His key achievements included developing &amp;amp; executing Strategic Initiatives, M&amp;amp;A activities, Project Implementation, Control &amp;amp; Cost reduction, Organization Culture change etc. In the initial stages of his career, he worked as a Management Consultant with Arthur Anderson in their Energy, Infrastructure and Industrial practices. Mr. Uplenchwar holds an MBA from Maastricht University, Netherlands. He is a Mechanical Engineer and has done his Post Graduation in Marine Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>IMG_9966_20180228_055733.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-02-28T17:57:34+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-01-31T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-02-28T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12999</productid>
    <productname>HCC Awarded Pune Metro Rail Project (2nd order)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January&amp;nbsp;08, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;HCC, as a lead partner in the joint venture with AL FARA&amp;rsquo;A, has been awarded a contract by the Maharashtra Metro Rail Corporation Ltd for Pune Metro Rail&amp;nbsp;Project&amp;nbsp; - Line 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The contract is for construction of eight elevated metro stations excluding viaduct and is to be completed in 110 weeks (26 months). This is the 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;contract win by HCC for Pune Metro Rail Project.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>PuneMetro2ndorder_20180228_055450.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-02-28T17:54:50.487+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2018-01-08T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-02-28T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12995</productid>
    <productname>Foundation Stone Laying of Parwan Gravity Dam Project</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p class="Bodycopy" style="margin-top: 0cm; tab-stops: center 2.85pt;"&gt;&lt;span class="BodyCopy0"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-GB" style="font-size: 9.0pt; letter-spacing: -.15pt;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December 15, 2018:&lt;/strong&gt; Union Minister of Road Transport and Highways Shri Nitin Gadkari and Chief Minister of Rajasthan Smt. Vasundhara Raje laid the foundation stone of Parwan Gravity Dam on December 15, 2017. HCC as a lead partner in joint venture with HSEPL has been awarded this EPC contract worth Rs 672.99 crore by the Water Resources Department, Government of Rajasthan. The project envisages construction of a concrete gravity dam and 8.475 km long tunnel for irrigation and water supply purpose involving civil, hydro-mechanical and electrical works on EPC basis. A 21km long access road will also be constructed to the project site. Once completed, the dam will provide drinking water to over 820 villages and irrigate over 1.38 lakh hectare land in Baran, Jhalavar and Kota district of Rajasthan. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>3_20180228_010726.png</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-02-28T13:07:26.647+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-15T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12994</productid>
    <productname>First TBM at Mumbai Metro 3 successfully launched</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December 04, 2017:&lt;/strong&gt; After months of geotechnical investigations, planning and a lengthy procurement phase, HCC Metro Project Line 3 Pkg 2 team successfully launched the first of the two TBMs from the project site at Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus in Mumbai on December 04, 2017. This event was graced by the presence of Mrs. Ashwini Bhide, Managing Director, Mumbai Metro Rail Corporation and senior bureaucrats from State and Central Government, BMC and MMRCL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The TBM is expected to record an average drilling rate of around 13 meters per day over the course of its 4.049 km drive from Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus to Mumbai Central via the station boxes at Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus, Kalbadevi, Girgaon and Grant Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The launch of TBM is a complex process and is done in 3 sections over a period of 7 to 8 weeks. The first phase is Initial Drive during which the Cutter Head, Shield Body and the Tail Shield body are lowered in the launch shaft. These three sections of around 20 meters are then joined together. The cutter head starts drilling and simultaneously moves in the rock body. During this drive, the TBM moves on a narrow gauge rail line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second phase is Transfer Drive during which the back-up gantries are lowered in the launch shaft. Then these gantries are pulled in the tunnel created by the cutter head and connected with it. A broad gauge rail line is required in this phase because the gantries are bigger in size and the locomotive used for the transportation of muck needs to fit in the gantries. The last and final phase is Main Drive, during this the rest of the parts are lowered and connected. In this phase, the TBM is ready to be fully operational.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The initial drive for the first TBM launched was completed on January 11, 2018 and the Main Drive started in the 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; week of February 2018. This TBM requires around 32 people to operate, which includes TBM operators, engineers and labours. Terratec, the manufactures of the TBM will provide support to the TBM Team for initial 6 months or 150 meters length drilling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first Tunnel Boring Machines (TBMs) being used at the Mumbai Metro Project Line 3 Pkg 2 had arrived at the site location in September 2017 and the second one arrived in December 2017. Manufactured in China, these TBM&amp;rsquo;s are Single Shield dual-mode hard rock TBM. They are equipped to operate in both, open or closed mode, in the predominantly fresh and slightly to moderately weathered Basalt and Breccia that are anticipated in the Mumbai Metro project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After arrival at Mumbai Port, transportation of the TBM from the BPT Orange gate to the project site at CST was a dunting task. Due to the enormous size of the TBM, the entire process of transportation was thoroughly planned to take into consideration every single obstacle on the way for the smooth movement. Despite challenges, the project team carried out the entire operation with utmost precision.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DSC_0013Large_20180228_055103.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-02-28T13:04:12.483+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-04T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>News</categoryname>
    <cattype>A</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12956</productid>
    <productname>TESTS MEETING REMINDER</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;TESTS MEETING REMINDERTESTS MEETING REMINDER&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage />
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-13T19:11:12.33+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-09-24T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2021-01-07T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Meetings</categoryname>
    <cattype>E</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12931</productid>
    <productname>NDTV 24x7 - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Realty Check)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;October 10, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/6AJIT GULABCHAND (HCC) NDTV 24X7 051017 2130PM.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:36:00.35+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12930</productid>
    <productname>Zee Business - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Lending rates by RBI)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;October 05, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/5AJIT GULABCHAND (HCC) ZB 051017 1210PM.mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:33:30.13+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12929</productid>
    <productname>CNBC - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Q4 Results 2016-17)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;May 05, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/4CNBC 050517 0940AM (Q4 Results).mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:31:55.007+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12928</productid>
    <productname>BTVi - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Budget 2017)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;February 03, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/3BTVI 030217 1915PM (Budget 2017).mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:30:35.97+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12927</productid>
    <productname>CNBC - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Budget 2017)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;February 01, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/2CNBC 010217 1537PM (Budget 2017).mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:29:41.837+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12926</productid>
    <productname>CNBC - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Davos 2017)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;January 17, 2017&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/1CNBC 170117 1505PM(Davos 2017).mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:28:29.647+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12919</productid>
    <productname>CNN IBN - Interview of Mr. Ajit Gulabchand (Leader Talk)</productname>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;March 27, 2016&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage>video.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed />
    <movietrailorcode>http://192.168.1.224:8082/files/mp4/cmdinterviews/3CNN IBN 270316 1130AM (Leader Talk).mp4</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2018-01-02T16:07:42.957+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1 />
    <startdate>2018-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename />
    <categoryname>Interviews</categoryname>
    <cattype>V</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12883</productid>
    <productname>Kachchh Branch Canal</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>_KBCInauguration_20181027_084350.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:13:13.413+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12877</productid>
    <productname>Maroshi Ruparel Water Supply Tunnel</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MaroshiRuparelWaterTunnel1_20181027_085706.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:12:57.377+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12867</productid>
    <productname>Polavaram Right Main Canal, Package III</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>PolavaramCanal1_20181027_085018.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:12:45.81+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12856</productid>
    <productname>Godavari Lift Irrigation Scheme</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>1GLISIntakeatGangaram_20181027_083842.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:12:27.073+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12851</productid>
    <productname>Saurashtra Branch Canal</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>SaurashtraBranchCanal1_20181027_085452.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:12:08.11+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12844</productid>
    <productname>Tirupur Water Supply Project</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>TirupurWaterSupplyProject1_20181027_085530.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:11:55.187+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12831</productid>
    <productname>Middle Vaitarna Pipeline</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MiddleVaitarnaPipeline1_20181027_084825.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:10:55.98+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12827</productid>
    <productname>Idukki Dam</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>IdukkiDam1_20181027_084247.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:10:14.813+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12826</productid>
    <productname>Bhandup Treatment Complex</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BhandupWTP_20181027_083557.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:09:59.67+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12822</productid>
    <productname>BMC Water Tunnel</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BMCWaterTunnel1_20181027_090108.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:09:43.823+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12819</productid>
    <productname>Farakka Barrage</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>FarakkaBarrage1_20181027_083701.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:09:23.197+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12813</productid>
    <productname>Gomti Aqueduct</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>GomtiAcqueduct_20181027_083937.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:08:15.857+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12808</productid>
    <productname>Hathnikund Barrage</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>HathnikundBarrage1_20181027_084211.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:07:54.78+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12803</productid>
    <productname>Kolkewadi Dam</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>KolkewadiDam1_20181027_084545.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:07:25.293+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12802</productid>
    <productname>Pune Water Treatment Plant</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MGDSewageTreatmentPlant_20181027_085324.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:06:07.803+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12797</productid>
    <productname>Sharda and Ghogra Barrage</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>ShardaBarrage1_20181027_085359.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:05:43.933+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12792</productid>
    <productname>Vaitarna Dam</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>VaitarnaDam_20181027_085620.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T12:05:20.573+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Water Solutions</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12766</productid>
    <productname>Bogibeel Rail-cum-Road Bridge</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BogibeelRailcumRoadBridge1_20181027_094510.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:55:59.083+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12745</productid>
    <productname>Bandra Worli Sea Link</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BWSL1_20181027_094226.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:55:40.77+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12731</productid>
    <productname>Mumbai Metro One</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>MumbaiMetroOne1_20181027_015816.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:55:10.36+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12719</productid>
    <productname>DMRC CC34</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>IMG_7042Edit2_20181027_100339.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:54:51.97+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12716</productid>
    <productname>DMRC CC30</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>IMG_0520_edit_20181027_100242.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:54:39.06+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12711</productid>
    <productname>DMRC AMEL C1 and C6</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DMRCAMELC11_20181027_100533.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:54:23.693+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12703</productid>
    <productname>Pirpanjal Railway Tunnel</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>PirPanjalRailTunnel1_20181027_020340.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:53:56.537+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12681</productid>
    <productname>Delhi Faridabad Elevated Expressway</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DFHL1_20181027_095204.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:53:14.923+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12672</productid>
    <productname>Naini Cable Stayed Bridge</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>NainiBridge1_20181027_015931.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:52:54.11+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12642</productid>
    <productname>Assam Road (NH54)</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>AssamRoad1_20181027_093909.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:52:25.64+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12637</productid>
    <productname>Kolkata Metro</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>KolkataMetro1_20181027_015356.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:52:02.42+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12628</productid>
    <productname>Lucknow Muzzafarpur National Highway Project</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>LMNHP1_20181027_102848.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:51:45.31+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12616</productid>
    <productname>Dhule Palesner Road</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>DhulePalesnar1_20181027_101019.JPG</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:51:13.79+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12610</productid>
    <productname>Allahabad Bypass </productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>allahabadbypass1_20181027_093028.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:50:40.57+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-24T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12607</productid>
    <productname>Bhor Ghat Tunnel</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>BhorghatTunnel_20181027_094402.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:50:24.347+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12604</productid>
    <productname>Saraighat Bridge</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>SairaighatBridge1_20181027_094627.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:50:08.503+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12599</productid>
    <productname>AP8</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>AP81_20181027_102616.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:49:52.17+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
  <Table1>
    <indexid>150171</indexid>
    <emailid>intranet@creativewebmall.com</emailid>
    <fullname>Demo User</fullname>
    <coverphoto>carlos.jpg</coverphoto>
    <gender>F</gender>
    <DOB>1995-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</DOB>
    <profilephoto>carlos.jpg</profilephoto>
    <productid>12594</productid>
    <productname>Chennai Bypass</productname>
    <shortdescription />
    <smallimage>N/A</smallimage>
    <bigimage>chennaiBypass1_20181027_095049.jpg</bigimage>
    <visitcount>0</visitcount>
    <viewstatus>S</viewstatus>
    <videoembed>N/A</videoembed>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
    <status>R</status>
    <createdon>2017-12-30T11:49:22.17+05:30</createdon>
    <createdby>intranet@creativewebmall.com</createdby>
    <product_year />
    <videoembed1>N/A</videoembed1>
    <startdate>2017-12-30T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2050-12-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>N/A</filename>
    <categoryname>Transportation</categoryname>
    <cattype>I</cattype>
  </Table1>
</NewDataSet>