<NewDataSet>
  <product>
    <productid>160470</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage />
    <productname>celebration</productname>
    <createdby>creativetest@gmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2017-01-11T17:17:02.597+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription />
    <startdate>2017-01-11T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2017-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <videoembed />
    <filename>Celebration.pdf_20170111_051701.pdf</filename>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
  </product>
  <product>
    <productid>160342</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage />
    <productname>Discover Mumbai : (The City, That Never Rest)</productname>
    <createdby>creativetest@gmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2016-11-14T17:29:32.507+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription>&lt;h2&gt;Promoting Mumbai&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;section class="leftSideBanner"&gt;&lt;img title="Promoting Mumbai" src="http://csia.in/assets/images/promoting_mumbai_top.jpg" alt="Promoting Mumbai" /&gt;&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mumbai, the City of Experiences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all its chaos, Mumbai is a thriving and lively city, producing more wealth and culture than any other city in India; there is no doubt that Mumbai in the 21st century is a tremendously exciting place to be. Over the last few years, a high-profile magazine has launched every couple of months, new newspapers have been set, dozens of new television channels have started operations and voluminous books about the city have invigorated international interest in Mumbai. New art galleries have opened up and well-established Indian artists are increasingly using Mumbai as an element in their works. The city&amp;rsquo;s nightclubs play the global cool of house and trance and home-grown mishmash of remixed Bollywood meets electronica via hip hop as well. The country's first symphony orchestra was formed in Mumbai in 2006. New clubs that fly down international acts are packed every night and major pop and rock stars have started including Mumbai on their world tour schedules. For the global traveller, flying in to Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s spanking new international terminal, the city has never been more attractive. Mumbai offers the unique experience of being not one city but many worlds: exhilarating, disheartening, charming, revolting, addictive, unfathomable and uncontrollable, but never boring.&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <startdate>2016-11-14T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2017-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <videoembed />
    <filename>testdoc.doc</filename>
    <movietrailorcode>N/A</movietrailorcode>
  </product>
  <product>
    <productid>120296</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage />
    <productname>News letter Teaser 1</productname>
    <createdby>creativetest@gmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2016-09-27T11:10:04.5+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;News letter Teaser 1&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <startdate>2016-09-27T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2017-01-31T23:59:59+05:30</enddate>
    <videoembed />
    <filename>dummy.pdf</filename>
  </product>
  <product>
    <productid>120295</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <productname>**** news letter</productname>
    <createdby>creativetest@gmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2016-09-16T17:10:37.37+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;**** news letter&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <startdate>2016-09-16T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2016-09-17T00:00:00+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>melgain_press_release.pdf</filename>
  </product>
  <product>
    <productid>110206</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <productname>new and upgraded csia </productname>
    <createdby>mailto.krishnasawant@rediffmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2016-07-19T12:07:24.61+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription>he year 2006 witnessed a momentous change 
for the airports in india with the privatization of mumbai&amp;#8217;s chhatrapati
 shivaji international 
                        airport (csia). on 3rd may 2006, the consortium,
 led by gvk took over the operations to modernize and redevelop csia. 
                   
                   &lt;section class="airlineinfosection"&gt;
                    &lt;section class="ul_content1"&gt; 
                   &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="border-bottom:0px;"&gt; new and upgraded csia &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
                   		&lt;p&gt;
                        &lt;img src="http://csia.in/assets/images/introduction_inner_right_img_mial.jpg" style="float: right; border: 4px solid #f8e497;height: auto; margin:0 0 5px 15px;" alt="about mial" title="about mial"&gt;
                        the modernization and redevelopment of csia is a
 reflection of india&amp;#8217;s 
                        rapid growth. being in the financial capital and
 a key gateway of the country, the redevelopment of csia holds great 
significance in aiding the city to
                         retain its fast paced growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
					     the transformation of csia, a brown-field project, is a 
one-of-its-kind unique infrastructural project in the world, unlike any 
other airport development projects.
                       &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
                        with a vision to become one of the world&amp;#8217;s best 
airports, mial has been continuously and consistently upgrading csia to 
an airport that delights its
                         guests by offering best in-class comfort and 
convenience.
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;
                       
                        in order to achieve a global standard, mial has 
partnered with well-known international experts for airport design and 
operations. csia handled traffic of 36.6 million passengers and around 
694 thousand tonnes of cargo in the fy 2014-2015.

                  
                     &lt;/p&gt;   
                     &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="border-bottom:0px;"&gt;csia's identity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
                      &lt;p&gt;csia&amp;#8217;s visual identity has been an integral 
part of its modernization process. with the launch of csia&amp;#8217;s new face, 
                     it became the first indian airport to receive a 
unique visual identity. derived from a peacock feather, the acronym 
&amp;#8216;csia&amp;#8217; has been woven 
                     seamlessly in the logo. the new identity symbolizes
 the three essential attributes: pride in india, people of india and 
global standards.&lt;/p&gt;
                   &lt;/section&gt; 
                   &lt;/section&gt;</shortdescription>
    <startdate>2016-07-19T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2016-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</enddate>
    <filename>tstpdf.pdf</filename>
  </product>
  <product>
    <productid>90167</productid>
    <categoryid>29</categoryid>
    <categoryname>News Letter</categoryname>
    <smallimage />
    <bigimage />
    <productname>Awards &amp; Accolades : over the years, gvk csia has turned into a truly global airport.</productname>
    <createdby>creativetest@gmail.com</createdby>
    <createdon>2016-06-03T18:30:33.573+05:30</createdon>
    <shortdescription>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;over the years, gvk csia has turned into a truly global airport. we have upgraded and modernized this airport to meet international standards in terms of service, technology and facilities. mial has received several international and national accolades for its efforts in modernizing gvk csia:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has been voted as the best airport in india and central asia by skytrax world airport awards 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has been inducted in the acrex hall of fame for its world class design, architecture, infrastructure and operational efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk mial has been rated as the world's best airport in the 25-40 million passengers per year category by aci in the airport service quality awards 2015.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk mial has bagged the 'cargo airport of the year &amp;ndash; region india' award for the second consecutive year at the 'stat trade times international awards' for excellence in air cargo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has become the first brownfield airport to receive the 'greenco gold rating'.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk mial&amp;rsquo;s cargo division has bagged the 'air cargo terminal award 2014-15' at the economic times logistics awards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk mial has been awarded the 'best airport - national' for excellence in connecting air cargo community&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;'air cargo agents association of india' &amp;nbsp;during the 42nd acaai annual convention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has been selected as the 'world's leading airport lounge - first class' at the world travel awards 2015.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has been awarded the golden peacock national award for risk management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia has been rated as the 'smar**** airport building in india' and the 'smar**** building in india' at the recently concluded &amp;lsquo;times of india and honeywell smart building awards&amp;rsquo; for 2015.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gvk csia&amp;rsquo;s has bagged the &amp;lsquo;innovation in tunnels award&amp;rsquo; for its proposed airside road tunnel project at the third arabian tunnelling conference &amp;amp; exhibition 2015, dubai.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</shortdescription>
    <startdate>2016-06-03T00:00:00+05:30</startdate>
    <enddate>2016-10-31T00:00:00+05:30</enddate>
    <videoembed />
    <filename>dummy.pdf</filename>
  </product>
</NewDataSet>